Bruno Criado

Winnipeg, MB, Canada brunocriado@gmail.com Phone: +1 431 588 3334

Summary

Seasoned Infrastructure Engineer with over a decade of experience working mostly with Servers and Services Management, Scripting, IT Networking and, since 2015, working closely with Cloud Computing, Microservices and Infrastructure as Code.

For 3 years worked as Backend Software Engineer using Python and C language with focus on Linux Operating System Management.

Also, in 2014, got a Post-Secondary Degree in Information Security by the Catholic University of Brasilia in Brazil.

Skills Base

Programming Languages: Python, C

Configuration Management Tools: Ansible, SaltStack Orchestration/Provisioning Tools: Terraform, SaltStack Container Tools: Docker, Docker Swarm, Registry Cloud Computing: AWS, Digital Ocean, OpenStack

CI/CD: Jenkins, Blue/Green Deployment Strategy, Canary Deployment Strategy Monitoring: ELK Stack, Grafana, Prometheus/Alertmanager Stack, Sensu

Education

Catholic University of Brasilia, Post-Secondary Degree in Information Security

Industry Experience

Site Reliability Engineer (SRE)

Aug 2018 - Present

SkipTheDishes - https://www.skipthedishes.com

Main Technologies: AWS, Python, terraform, Prometheus, Graphite, Grafana

Responsibilities:

- Providing visibility of our production services through metrics and graphs.
- Automation of menial tasks helping out developers in deployment and migration tasks
- Being solution oriented and sharing ownership with developers

Infrastructure Developer

Nov 2015 - Mar 2018

Flugel.it - https://www.flugel.it

Main Technologies: AWS, Python, terraform, ansible, ELK Stack, DevOps Tools, Docker

Responsibilities:

- Automating and implementing solutions using script languages and DevOps Tools
- Creating and developing system to aggregate value to client products
- Building and Deploying Infrastructure

Software Engineer

Sep 2012 - Aug 2015

MStech - http://www.mstech.com.br

Main Technologies: Linux, Python, C/C++, Virtualization.

Responsibilities:

- Maintain a multi-platform solution for remote boot and hard disk protection on storage virtualization
- Maintaining a Linux distribution for hard drive imaging purpose
- Developing products for managing classrooms

	Senior IT Infrastructure Analyst Fidelity Information Service - https://www.fisglobal.com	May 2011 - Jul 2012
	IT Infrastructure Analyst Eprom - http://www.eprom.com.br	Jan 2010 - Apr 2011
	IT Infrastructure Analyst Inforeason - http://www.inforeason.com.br	Mar 2009 - Dec 2009
	IT Infrastructure Analyst Lecom - http://www.lecom.com.br	Aug 2008 - Mar 2009
	IT Infrastructure Analyst Inforeason - http://www.inforeason.com.br	Mar 2007 - Aug 2008
	IT Intern Neobiz	Mar 2004 - Aug 2005
Teaching Experience	Professor Senac - IT Technical College http://sp.senac.br/bauru	Sep 2009 - Apr 2011
	Professor Senac - IT Technical College http://sp.senac.br/jau	Sep 2006 - Apr 2008
More Info	• Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/in/brunocriado • Github: https://github.com/brunocriado	